<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="105">
    <author>NX Modding</author>
    <version>1.0.0.1</version>
    <title>
        <en>NX Productions</en>
        <de>Produktionsübersicht</de>
        <fr>NX Productions</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[View all your productions with fill types, capacities, and monthly income.
        
Press R Shift + P to open the Production Overview.
Logo: MarkThor
v1.0.0.1 Changelog:
Logistics screen:
- And Production name and recipe is also contained on this page
Supply Duration:
- Accounts for shared consumption - Multiple recipes using the same input
- Uses actual consumption rates - Based on cyclesPerHour
- Finds the bottleneck - Calculates based on which input is likely to run out first e.g. if multiple recipes use the same input
Cycles/MO:
- Simply highlights how many cycles er month the recipe is outputting if inputs and outputs are maintained
Output Mode:
- Showcases which mode the recipe is set to e.g. Storing, Selling, Distributing
Location:
- This shows where the product which recipe is set too distributing. (Note: Only if output mode distributing is selected)
- If set to Storing or selling this will display as N/A in Red
Status:
Status's may appear to be delayed, this is not the case it is the game syncing the change in status to the game. If you reload the window or alter another recipe it will update. This is out of our hands and is down to how the game processes changes.
- "Active" (Green) - Recipe is running AND has inputs available
- "Active (!)" (Orange) - Recipe is set to active BUT missing inputs (game has paused it)
- "Inactive" (Red) - Recipe is manually deactivated by the player
Bug Fix's
- Fixed: (Production rows now dynamically calculated based on number of fill types, inputs/outputs and also recipe count)
v1.0.0.0 Changelog:
- Production Overview: View all productions with fill levels, capacities, monthly income and processing type.
- Toggle Views: Switch between inputs, outputs, and recipes
- Financial Tracking: See monthly revenue, costs, and net profit for each production
- Auto-Management: Automatically activate/deactivate productions based on input availability and output capacity
- CSV Export: Export all production data for external analysis
- Multi-Language Support: Available in 12 languages
]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Zeige alle deine Produktionen mit Füllarten, Kapazitäten und monatlichem Einkommen an.
        
Drücke R Shift + P, um die Produktionsübersicht zu öffnen.
Logo: MarkThor
v1.0.0.1 Änderungen:
Logistik-Bildschirm:
- Produktionsname und Rezept sind auf dieser Seite enthalten
Vorratsdauer:
- Berücksichtigt gemeinsamen Verbrauch - Mehrere Rezepte verwenden denselben Eingang
- Verwendet tatsächliche Verbrauchsraten - Basierend auf Zyklen pro Stunde
- Findet den Engpass - Berechnet basierend darauf, welcher Eingang zuerst leer wird
Zyklen/Monat:
- Zeigt wie viele Zyklen pro Monat das Rezept ausgibt, wenn Ein- und Ausgänge aufrechterhalten werden
Ausgabemodus:
- Zeigt an, auf welchen Modus das Rezept eingestellt ist, z.B. Lagern, Verkaufen, Verteilen
Standort:
- Zeigt an, wohin das Produkt verteilt wird (Hinweis: Nur wenn Ausgabemodus "Verteilen" ausgewählt ist)
- Wenn auf "Lagern" oder "Verkaufen" eingestellt, wird "N/A" in Rot angezeigt
Status:
Status-Änderungen können verzögert erscheinen. Dies liegt am Synchronisationsprozess des Spiels. Bei Neuladen des Fensters oder Änderung eines anderen Rezepts wird der Status aktualisiert. Dies liegt außerhalb unserer Kontrolle.
- "Aktiv" (Grün) - Rezept läuft UND hat verfügbare Eingänge
- "Aktiv (!)" (Orange) - Rezept ist aktiv ABER Eingänge fehlen (Spiel hat es pausiert)
- "Inaktiv" (Rot) - Rezept wurde manuell vom Spieler deaktiviert
Fehlerbehebungen:
- Behoben: Produktionszeilen werden nun dynamisch basierend auf Anzahl der Füllarten, Ein-/Ausgänge und Rezeptanzahl berechnet
v1.0.0.0 Änderungen:
- Produktionsübersicht: Zeige alle Produktionen mit Füllständen, Kapazitäten, monatlichem Einkommen und Verarbeitungstyp
- Ansichten umschalten: Wechsel zwischen Eingängen, Ausgängen und Rezepten
- Finanzverfolgung: Siehe monatliche Einnahmen, Kosten und Nettogewinn für jede Produktion
- Automatische Verwaltung: Automatisches Aktivieren/Deaktivieren von Produktionen basierend auf Eingangsverfügbarkeit und Ausgangskapazität
- CSV-Export: Exportiere alle Produktionsdaten für externe Analyse
- Mehrsprachige Unterstützung: Verfügbar in 12 Sprachen
]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Visualisez toutes vos productions avec les types de remplissage, les capacités et les revenus mensuels.
        
Appuyez sur R Shift + P pour ouvrir l'aperçu des productions.
Logo: MarkThor
v1.0.0.1 Modifications :
Écran logistique :
- Le nom de la production et la recette sont également contenus sur cette page
Durée d'approvisionnement :
- Prend en compte la consommation partagée - Plusieurs recettes utilisant la même entrée
- Utilise les taux de consommation réels - Basé sur les cycles par heure
- Trouve le goulot d'étranglement - Calcule en fonction de l'entrée susceptible de s'épuiser en premier
Cycles/Mois :
- Indique simplement combien de cycles par mois la recette produit si les entrées et sorties sont maintenues
Mode de sortie :
- Affiche le mode dans lequel la recette est définie, par exemple Stockage, Vente, Distribution
Emplacement :
- Cela montre où le produit de la recette est distribué (Note : Uniquement si le mode de sortie Distribution est sélectionné)
- Si défini sur Stockage ou Vente, cela s'affichera comme N/A en rouge
Statut :
Les statuts peuvent sembler retardés, ce n'est pas le cas, c'est le jeu qui synchronise le changement de statut. Si vous rechargez la fenêtre ou modifiez une autre recette, le statut se mettra à jour. Cela échappe à notre contrôle et dépend de la façon dont le jeu traite les changements.
- "Actif" (Vert) - La recette fonctionne ET a des entrées disponibles
- "Actif (!)" (Orange) - La recette est active MAIS il manque des entrées (le jeu l'a mise en pause)
- "Inactif" (Rouge) - La recette est désactivée manuellement par le joueur
Corrections de bugs :
- Corrigé : Les lignes de production sont maintenant calculées dynamiquement en fonction du nombre de types de remplissage, d'entrées/sorties et du nombre de recettes
v1.0.0.0 Modifications :
- Aperçu des productions : Visualisez toutes les productions avec les niveaux de remplissage, les capacités, les revenus mensuels et le type de traitement
- Basculer les vues : Basculez entre les entrées, les sorties et les recettes
- Suivi financier : Consultez les revenus mensuels, les coûts et le bénéfice net pour chaque production
- Gestion automatique : Active/désactive automatiquement les productions en fonction de la disponibilité des entrées et de la capacité de sortie
- Export CSV : Exportez toutes les données de production pour une analyse externe
- Support multilingue : Disponible en 12 langues
]]></fr>
    </description>
    
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n"/>
    <iconFilename>icon_NXProductionsOverview.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="ProductionOverview.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="RegisterPlayerActionEvents.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="ProductionSettings.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="ProductionAutoManager.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <actions>
        <action name="SHOW_PRODUCTION_DLG" category="SYSTEM" />
    </actions>  
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="SHOW_PRODUCTION_DLG">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rshift KEY_p" />
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding> 
    
</modDesc>